<author>TLR. Mengko,</author><title>"Meat Structure Imaging and Visualization Using u CT ",</title><booktitle>ICBEMA</booktitle><date>9-10 Nov 2012,</date><publisher>Swiss Jerman University</publisher>
<author>TLR. Mengko, Kastam Astami,</author><title>"Development Progress of Android Based Personal ECG System ",</title><booktitle>ICBEMA</booktitle><date>9-10 Nov 2012,</date><publisher>Swiss Jerman University</publisher>
<author>A. Kurniawan,</author><title>“Teknik Deteksi Multiuser pada Sistem CDMA,”</title><event>Seminar Nasional Forum Pendidikan Tinggi Teknik Elektro Indonesia (FORTEI) 2014,</event><location>Bandung</location><date>2-4 Juni 2014.</date>
<author>Baso Maruddani, A Kurniawan, Sugihartono, Achmad Munir,</author><title>“Prediction method for rain rate and rain propagation attenuation for K-band satellite communication link at tropical area,”</title><journal>Journal of ICT Research And Application,</journal><volume>Vol. 8C No. 1,</volume><date>2014.</date>
<author>Umar Khayam , Masahiro Kozako, Masayuki Hikita, Tosihiro Hoshino, Shiro Maruyama, Junichi Wada and Shigemitsu Okabe,</author><title>“Effect of the Presence of Epoxy Spacer on Transmission Rate of Electromagnetic Wave Propagating through T-Branch of 66 kV GIS Model Tank”,</title><journal>IEEE Transactions on Dielectric and Electrical Insulation,</journal><volume>Volume 20 Issue 6,</volume><pages>pp. 2254-2261,</pages><date>December 2013.</date>
<author>Umar Khayam ,</author><title>”Analysis of Distribution, Pattern, and Vector of Electric Field in the Inter Phases Region of Three-phase Gas Insulated Switchgear”,</title><journal>International Journal on Electrical Engineering and Informatics –</journal><volume>Volume 5, Number 4,</volume><pages>pp. 492-500,</pages><date>December 2013.</date>
<date>[2016]</date><author>T.L. Achmad, W.-X Fu, H. Chen, C. Zhang, Z.-G. Yang,</author><title>First-principles calculations of generalized-stacking-fault-energy of Co-based alloys,</title><journal>Comput. Mater. Sci. 121</journal><pages>pp. 86–96.</pages><publisher>(Elsevier).</publisher><url>http://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.commatsci.2016.04.031</url>
<date>[2015]</date><author>Sanwani E., Mirahati R.Z., Chaerun S.K.</author><title>Possible role of the biosurfactant-producing- and Fe-S-oxidizing bacterium in silicate and sulfide bioflotation processes.</title><journal>Advanced Materials Research,</journal><volume>Vol. 1130,</volume><pages>pp. 493-498</pages>
<date>[2015]</date><author>Sanwani E., Wahyuningsih T., Chaerun S.K.</author><title>Assessment of surface properties of silica-bacterial cell complex: a potential application for silicate bioflotation processes.</title><journal>Advanced Materials Research,</journal><volume>Vol. 1130,</volume><pages>pp. 515-518</pages>
<booktitle>Proceedings of The 12th Symposium on Fracture and Fracture Mechanics, The Society of Materials Science, Japan,</booktitle><pages>pp. 121-125.</pages><date>October 17-18, 2005,</date><location>Hamamatsu, Japan.</location><title>“In-situ SEM Observation of Constant-DK Fatigue Crack Growth Behavior in Ferritic-Pearlitic Steels with Various Pearlite Morphologies”</title><author>(Akhmad A. Korda, Y. Miyashita, Y. Mutoh and T. Sadasue)</author>
<booktitle>Proceedings of The 55th The Annual Meetings of The Society of Materials Science, Japan,</booktitle><pages>pp. 81-82.</pages><date>May 27, 2006,</date><location>Nagaoka, Japan.</location><title>“Effects of Pearlite Morphology on Fatigue Crack Growth Resistance in Ferritic-Pearlitic Steels”</title><author>(Akhmad A. Korda, Y. Mutoh, Y. Miyashita and T. Sadasue)</author>
<author>Wikaningtyas, P., Sukandar, E.Y., Retnoningrum, D.S., Parwati, I.</author><title>“A multicenter surveillance and reporting of antimicrobial resistance: Focus on Ceftriaxone-resistant Escherichia coli in the year 2012 and 2013”;</title><journal>International Journal of Pharmaceutical and Clinical Research</journal><volume>8 (7),</volume><pages>pp. 685-689″</pages>
<author>Ismaya, W.T., Yunita, Efthyani, A., Lai, X., Retnoningrum, D.S, Rachmawati, H., Dijkstra, B.W., Tjandrawinata, R.R.,</author><title>“A novel immune-tolerable and permeable lectin-like protein from mushroom Agaricus bisporus”;</title><journal>Biochemical and Biophysical Research Communications,</journal><volume>473 (4),</volume><pages>pp. 1090-1093</pages>
<author>Heni Rachmawati, Dewa Ken Budiputra, Rachmat Mauludin,</author><title>Curcumin nanoemulsion for transdermal application: formulation and evaluation,</title><booktitle>Drug Development and Industrial Pharmacy,</booktitle><date>2015,</date><volume>41(4):</volume><pages>560-566</pages>
<author>Heni Rachmawati, Bernard Manuel Haryadi, Kusnandar Anggadiredja, Veinardi Suendo,</author><title>Intraoral Film Containing Insulin-Phospholipid Microemulsion: Formulation and In Vivo Hypoglycemic Activity Study,</title><journal>American Association of Pharmaceutical Scientists PharmTech,</journal><date>2015,</date><volume>16(3):</volume><pages>692-703.</pages>
<author>Jessie Sofia Pamudji, Rachmat Mauludin, Nurhabibah;</author><title>Influence of -cyclodextrin on Cefixime Stability in Liquid Suspension Dosage Form;</title><journal>”Procedia Chemistry , 2014;</journal><volume>13:</volume><pages>119-127″;</pages><date>2014</date>
<author>Jessie Sofia Pamudji, Saleh Wikarsa, Meisa Handini Tampara;</author><title>Improvement of Glicazide’s Dissolution Rate by Using Surface Solid Dispersion with Avicel PH 101;</title><journal>”Int J Pharm Pharmaceut Sci , 2014;</journal><volume>6(11):</volume><pages>461-465″;</pages><date>2014</date>
<author>Koesmawati TA, Buchari B, Sulaeman A, Ibrahim S;</author><title>Analytical performance of HG-QFAAS and ICP-MS in Determination of the Total Arsenic in Indonesia Tuna Fish Sample;</title><journal>International Journal of Basic &amp; Applied Sciences IJBAS-IJENS</journal><volume>Vol 13, No 01,</volume><date>February 2013,</date><pages>113-117.</pages>
<author>Oktariza, Y., Dwichandra Putra, O., Insanu, M., Musadad Miftah, A.;</author><title>The analytical application of cloud point extraction: A simple spectrophotometric method forselenium determination in Kangkong (Ipomoea reptans P.);</title><journal>International Journal of Pharmacy and Pharmaceutical Sciences,</journal><volume>Volume 5, Issue 4,</volume><date>2013,</date><pages>Pages 498-501</pages>
<author>Danu Ariono, Mubiar Purwasasmita, I Gede Wenten,</author><title>Brine Effluents: Characteristics, Environmental Impacts, and Theirs Handing,</title><journal>Journal of Engineering and Technological Sciences,</journal><volume>Volume 48 (4),</volume><pages>pp. 367-387,</pages><date>2016,</date><isbn>ISSN: 2337-5779, E-ISSN: 2338-5502</isbn><source>(Scopus)</source>
<author>Amalia Kartika, I., Evon, P., Cerny, M., Suparno, O., Hermawan, D., Ariono, D., Rigal, L.,</author><title>Simultaneous Solvent Extraction and Transesterification of Jatropha Oil for Biodiesel Production, and Potential application of the obtained cakes for binderless particleboard,</title><journal>Journal Fuel</journal><volume>Vol. 181,</volume><date>October 2016,</date><pages>pages 870-877,</pages><url>Journal homepage : www.elsevier.com/locate/fuel,</url><isbn>ISSN : 0016-2361, E-ISSN : 1873-7153,</isbn><source>(Scopus)</source>
<author>Abady, H., Joelianto, E.,</author><title>Energy aware distributed estimator system over wireless sensor networks with ad-hoc on-demand distance vector (AODV) routing algorithm,</title><journal>Internetworking Indonesia Journal,</journal><volume>Volume 8, Issue 1,</volume><date>2016,</date><pages>Pages 23-28,</pages><isbn>ISSN: 19429703</isbn><source>(Scopus)</source>
<author>Joelianto, E., Widyotriatmo, A., Turnip, A. ,</author><title>Guest editors’ introduction to special issue on Industrial Internet of Things (IIoT),</title><journal>Internetworking Indonesia Journal,</journal><volume>Volume 8, Issue 1,</volume><date>2016,</date><pages>Pages 1-3,</pages><isbn>ISSN: 1942-9703</isbn><source>(Scopus)</source>
<author>Ferry Rusgiyarto, Ade Sjafruddin, Russ Bona Frazila, and Suprayogi.,</author><title>Discrete Event Simulation Model for External Yard Choice of Import Container Terminal in a Port Buffer Area. Green Process, Material, and Energy: A Sustainable Solution for Climate Change:</title><booktitle>Proceedings of the 3rd International Conference on Engineering, Technology, and Industrial Application (ICETIA 2016).</booktitle><isbn>ISBN: 978-0-7354-1529-4.</isbn><booktitle>AIP Conf. Proc.</booktitle><isbn>1855-040014-8;</isbn><doi>doi: 10.1063/I_4985510</doi>
<author>Budhi, Y.W., Devianto, H., Ignacia, L., Mikhael, H.A.,</author><title>Process intensification of hydrogen production from Ethanol using microreactor,</title><booktitle>Proceedings – Joint International Conference on Electric Vehicular Technology and Industrial, Mechanical, Electrical and Chemical Engineering, ICEVT 2015 and IMECE 2015,</booktitle><date>20 June 2016,</date><note>Article number 7496650,</note><pages>Pages 47-52</pages><source>(Scopus)</source>
<author>Ferry Rusgiyarto, Ade Sjafruddin, Russ Bona Frazilla, Suprayogi,</author><title>BI-Level Programming pada Metode Optimasi Terminal Petikemas dan Jaringan Akses.</title><event>The International Symposium of Indonesian Inter-University Transport Studies Forum (FSTPT) – 18,</event><location>Unila, Bandar Lampung,</location><date>August 28th, 2015.</date><isbn>ISBN: 979-95721-12-18.</isbn><pages>Hal.: 805 – 813.</pages>
<author>David Bahrin, Subagjo dan Herri Susanto,</author><title>Penyusunan Kriteria Pemilihan Proses Flue Gas Desulfurization PLTU – Batubara,</title><booktitle>Prosiding Seminar Nasional Teknik Kimia “Kejuangan” Pengembangan Teknologi Kimia Untuk Pengolahan Sumber Daya Alam Indonesia,</booktitle><location>Yogyakarta,</location><date>18 Maret 2015.</date>
<author>Firman, T., Fahmi, F.Z..</author><title>The Privatization of Metropolitan Jakarta’s (Jabodetabek) Urban Fringes: The Early Stages of “Post-Suburbanization” in Indonesia,</title><journal>Journal of the American Planning Association.</journal><volume>83 (1),</volume><pages>pp. 68-79</pages>
<author>Tarigan, A.K.M., Samsura, D.A.A., Sagala, S., Wimbardana, R.</author><title>Balikpapan: Urban planning and development in anticipation of the post-oil industry era,</title><booktitle>Cities,</booktitle><volume>Volume 60, Part A,</volume><date>February 2017,</date><pages>Pages 246–259</pages>
<author>Yogi Makbul.</author><title>How much does rice price influence milled paddy price? Analysis of price integration in Indonesia,</title><journal>Journal of Archives of Business Research,</journal><volume>Vol 5, No 3</volume><date>(2017),</date><pages>page 238 – 247</pages>
<author>Yogi Makbul.</author><title>Analysis of The Integration of Rice and Paddy Prices in Indonesia Using a Vector Error Correction Model,</title><journal>Journal of Applied Bussiness and Economic Research,</journal><volume>Vol. 15, No. no. 10</volume><pages>page 209-218,</pages><isbn>ISSN : 0972-7302</isbn>
<author>Allis Nurdini, Ismet B. Harun.</author><title>Spatial bounded-choice behaviour within the consumer of rental housing in Bandung, Indonesia,</title><journal>Journal of ASIAN Behavioural Studies,</journal><date>01 April 2017,</date><isbn>E-ISSN: 2514-7528,</isbn><volume>Vol. 2, No. 3,</volume><pages>page: 95-104</pages>
<date>2000</date><title>"Subyek yang Tidak Berkehendak",</title><journal>Forum Keadilan,</journal><volume>No. 35,</volume><date>3 Desember 2000,</date><pages>hal. 46-47</pages>
<title>“Sudjana Kerton dalam Sejarah Seni Rupa Indonesia”, dalam “Sejarah Terpisah; Sudjana Kerton dan Seni Rupa Modern Indonesia”,</title><publisher>Penerbit Sanggar Luhur,</publisher><location>Bandung,</location><date>2004</date>
<title>Tungku gelas Melting Furnace sebagai upaya pengembangan studio gelas di FSRD ITB,</title><booktitle>Penelitian bidang seni rupa tahun 2005,</booktitle><publisher>LPPM ITB,</publisher><note>Anggota Peneliti</note><date>(2005)</date>
<author>Widyarini, M., Simatupang, T.M. and Engelseth, P.</author><date>(2016),</date><title>“Social Interaction and Price Transmission in Multi-Tier Food Supply Chains”,</title><journal>Journal of Operations and Supply Chain Management,</journal><volume>9 (1),</volume><pages>110-128.</pages><doi>DOI: http://dx.doi.org/10.12660/joscmv9n1p110-128</doi>
<author>Simatupang, T.M. and Sridharan, R.</author><date>(2016),</date><title>“A critical analysis of supply chain issues in construction heavy equipment”,</title><journal>International Journal of Construction Management,</journal><volume>16 (2),</volume><pages>1-13.</pages><doi>doi:10.1080/15623599.2016.1142250</doi>
<author>Nur Hasanah. E., Koesrindartoto, D., P.,</author><date>(2015),</date><title>“Understanding the Effects of Indonesia Credit Card Ownership Limitation Policy Through Customer Perspective in Online Forum”.</title><journal>Advanced Science Letters ,</journal><volume>21 (6),</volume><pages>1638-1642.</pages><doi>doi: http://dx.doi.org/10.1166/asl.2015.6237</doi>
<author>Dyah Hastuti, E.W., Made Emmy Suparka, S. Asikin and A.H. Harsolumakso,</author><date>2003,</date><title>Miocene Volcanism Related to Hydrothermal Alteration in ponorogo, East Java, Indonesia.</title><booktitle>Proceeding 8th Regional Committee on Pacific Neogene Statigraphy,</booktitle><location>Chiang Mai, Thailand,</location><date>2003.</date>
<author>Isnaniawardhani, Made Emmy Suparka , R. Kapid, and H. Latief,</author><date>2004,</date><title>Pliocene to Holocen Nannoplankton Climatostratigraphy (Case Study: Northern East Java Basin, Indonesia)”.</title><booktitle>The International Symposium on the Geologic Evolution of East and Southeast Asia,</booktitle><location>in Bangkok.</location>
<author>Dyah Hastuti, E. W., Made Emmy Suparka, S. Asikin, and A.H. Harsolumakso,</author><date>2003,</date><title>Miocene Volcanism Related to Hydrothermal Alteration in Ponorogo, East Java, Indonesia.</title><booktitle>Proceeding 8th Regional Committee on Pacific Neogene Stratigraphy,</booktitle><location>Chiang Mai, Thailand.</location>
<author>Noeradi D., Muritno B.P., Sukoeitono, Subroto E.A., dan Djuhaeni,</author><date>2005,</date><title>Petroleum system and hydrocarbon prospectivity of the Simenggaris Block and its surrounding areas, tarakan Basin, East Kalimantan, Indonesia: a new approach by using sequence stratigraphy.</title><booktitle>Proceedings AAPG 2005 International Conference,</booktitle><location>Paris.</location><note>Sedang dicetak.</note>
<author>Priadi B., Zulkarnain I, and Permana H.,</author><date>2004,</date><title>Volcanism and submarine hydrothermal activities around Krakatau island in Sunda Strait,</title><booktitle>Indonesia Proceedings 5th International Conference on Asian Marine Geology,</booktitle><location>bangkok Thailand.</location>
<author>Subroto, E.A., Muritno B.P., Sukowitono, Noeradi. D., dan Djuhaeni.,</author><date>2005,</date><title>Petroleum Geochemistry in a sequence stratugraphic framework in the Simenggaris Block, Tarakan Basin, East Kalimantan, Indonesia.</title><booktitle>Proc. Indonesia Petroleum Association 30th Annual &amp; Exhibition.</booktitle>
<author>Aswan, Yahdi Zaim, Tomowo Ozawa.,</author><date>2004,</date><title>A new species of Ampullonatica from the Eocene Nanggulan Formation, Central Jawa, Indonesia and its implication for Paleogene Tethyan biogeography.,</title><journal>Buletin Geologi,</journal><volume>Vol. 36, No. 1,</volume><pages>p. 15-20.</pages>
<author>Roy Larick, Russlell L. Ciochon, Yahdi Zaim,</author><date>2003,</date><title>“Homo erectus and the Emergence of Sunda in the Tethys realm, Contributions of Polassium chronology in the Sangiran dome, Central Java”</title><journal>Athena Review-USA.</journal><volume>Vol. 4, No. 1.</volume><pages>pp. 2-9.</pages>
<author>Abduh, M. Y.</author><title>Biobased products from rubber, jatropha and sunflower oil,</title><publisher>Unieversity of Groningen,</publisher><date>2015</date><isbn>(ISBN: 978-90-367-7644-8).</isbn>
<author>Abduh, M. Y., A. Fernandez, A. Kloekhorst, R. Manurung, H.J. Heeres.</author><title>Experimental and modelling studies on continuous synthesis and refining of biodiesel in a dedicated bench scale unit using centrifugal contactor separator technology.</title><journal>Eur. J. Lipid Sci. Technol.</journal><date>2015,</date><doi>DOI: 10.1002/ejlt.201500113</doi>
<author>Abduh, M. Y., W. V. Ulden, T. Buntara, H.H. van de Bovenkamp, F. Pichioni, R. Manurung, H.J. Heeres.</author><date>2015.</date><title>Synthesis and refining of sunflower biodiesel in a cascade of continuous centrifugal contactor separators.</title><journal>Eur. J. Lipid Sci. Technol.,</journal><date>2015,</date><volume>117,</volume><pages>242-254.</pages>
<author>Alwani, M.S., Abdulkhalil, H.P.S., Sulaiman, O., Islam, M.N., and Dungani, R..</author><date>2013.</date><title>An Approach to Using Agricultural Waste Fibres in Biocomposites Application: Thermogravimetric Analysis and Activation Energy Study.</title><journal>Journal of Bioresources</journal><volume>9(1),</volume><pages>218-230</pages>
<author>Anggraeni, T., Rahayu, S., Ahmad, I., Esyanti, R.R. and Putra, R.E.</author><title>2013.Resources Partitioning and Different Foraging Behavior could maintained coexistence of Thripshawaiiensis (Thysanoptera: Tripidae) and Elaeidobiuskamerunicus (Coleoptera : Curculionidae) On Oil Palm (ElaeisguineensisJacq) flower.</title><journal>Journal of Entomology and Nematology.</journal><volume>Vol 5(5)</volume><pages>pages 59-63</pages>
<author>M. Syaputra, S.A. Wella, A. Purqon, Suprijadi,</author><title>External and Internal Influences in Silicene Monolayer,</title><booktitle>Advanced Materials Research,</booktitle><volume>vol 1112,</volume><pages>pp 133-138</pages><date>(2015)</date>
<author>H. Nagao, S. Kawamoto, M. Rusmerryani, A. Purqon, K. Kawaguchi, H. Saito,</author><title>Molecular Dynamics Study on Entrainment Phenomenon in Model Molecular Systems, Slow Dynamics in Complex Systems,</title><booktitle>American Institute of Physics AIP Conference Proceeding,</booktitle><volume>vol 1518,</volume><pages>pp. 729-732</pages><date>(2013)</date>
<author>E. Aprilia, A. Purqon, Suprijadi,</author><title>The Geometrical Effects of Substitutional Impurities on Electric and Magnetic Properties of (10, 0) Carbon Nanotube by using Density Functional Theory</title><booktitle>Recent Development in Computational Science</booktitle><volume>vol 4 ,</volume><pages>pp 23-29</pages><date>(2013)</date>
<author>Rahma, M. M. Munir, Khairrurijal, A. Prasetyo, V. Suendo, H. Rachmawati,</author><title>Intermolecular Interactions and the Release Pattern of Electrospun Curcumin-Polyvinyl(pyrrolidone) Fiber,</title><journal>Biol. Pharm. Bull.</journal><volume>39: 2,</volume><date>(2016),</date><pages>163-173., http://doi.org/10.1248/bpb.b15-00391</pages>
<author>Abdullah, M.,</author><title>Proposal for a material with negative thermal expansion,</title><journal>J. Mod. Phys. B,</journal><volume>30,</volume><pages>1650238</pages><date>(2016).</date><pages>10.1142/S0217979216502386</pages>
<author>Aep Patah, Josua Baechle, Guenter Grampp,</author><title>Cations/Anions Effects of Imidazolium-based Ionic Liquids on the Diffusion Properties of Iron- and Ruthenium-bipyridine / Phenanthroline Complexes,</title><journal>Electrochimica Acta,</journal><volume>219,</volume><date>(2016),</date><pages>305 – 311,</pages><url>http://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.electacta.2016.10.010</url>
<author>Agus Yodi Gunawan, Kasbawati, Kuntjoro Adji Sidarto,</author><title>Approximate Solutions of Linearized Delay Differentiail Equations Arising from a Microbial Fermentation Process Using the Matrix Lambert Function,</title><journal>Journal of Mathematical and Fundamental Sciences,</journal><volume>48: 1, (2016),</volume><pages>25-38,</pages><date>2016.</date>
<title>Optimized 8level turbo encoder algorithm and VLSI architecture for LTE,</title><booktitle>Proceedings of the 2011 International Conference on Electrical Engineering and Informatics, ICEEI 2011(2011).</booktitle>
<title>Mechanical Behaviour of Offshore Pipeline Using Nickel Slag Agreggate and Fly Ash as Partial Cement Substitute,</title><booktitle>ACEC Conference,</booktitle><location>Pattaya, Thailand,</location><date>1213 March 2009 (2009).</date>
<title>Mechanical Behaviour of Offshore Pipeline Using Nickel Slag Agreggate and Fly Ash as Partial Cement Substitute,</title><booktitle>ACEC Conference,</booktitle><location>Pattaya, Thailand,</location><date>1213 March(2009).</date>
<title>The Control Design of Symmetric System for Tracking A Desired Path with An Obstacle Using Tracking Error Dynamics,</title><booktitle>Contributions in Mathematics and Applications III, A special volume 2010</booktitle><publisher>published by EastWest Journal of Mathematics(2011).</publisher>
<title>Thermodynamics study of flashbinary cycle in geothermal power plant,</title><booktitle>Renewable and Sustainable Energy Reviews(2011).</booktitle>
<title>Heating Value Improvement of Palm Emty Fruit Bunch as Solid Fuel Through , Torrrefaction Process,</title><booktitle>ICCHT 2008.</booktitle><date>(2008).</date>
<author>Ayu Purwarianti, Zulfikar Hakim,</author><title>"Interactive Question Answering for Customer Service Representative Using Information State Concept",</title><booktitle>2012 International Conference on System Engineering and Technology,</booktitle><date>September 11-12, 2012,</date><location>Bandung, Indonesia</location>
<author>Aqsath Rasyid Naradhipa, Ayu Purwarianti,</author><title>"Sentiment Classification for Indonesian Message in Social Media",</title><booktitle>International Conference on Cloud Computing and Social Networking,</booktitle><date>26-27 April 2012</date>
<author>Filman Ferdian, Ayu Purwarianti,</author><title>"Implementation of Semantic Analyzer in Indonesian Text-Understanding Evaluation System",</title><booktitle>IEEE International Conference on Computational Intelligence and Cybernetics,</booktitle><date>July 12-14, 2012</date>
